It's time for
"Celebrity Family Feud"!
Coming in for a slam dunk,
it's the
"Inside the NBA" Team,
playing for the
Mustard Seed School.
But watch out.
This team is ready
to hit it out of the park!
It's the MLB All-Star Team,
playing for Major League
Baseball charities.
And now the star of our show...
Steve Harvey!
♪♪
What's up, baby? Yeah!
-Yeah!
-That's what I'm talking about.
Yeah! You know it. You know it.
What's up? How you doing?
Everybody good?
What's up, Jimmy?
Johnny, how you feeling?
What's up, Sean?
What's up, Jennie?
What's up, John?
How you feelin'?
I like this one right here.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Good. I appreciate y'all.
Thank you very much.
I appreciate everybody.
Well, everybody, welcome
to "Celebrity Family Feud"!
I'm your man Steve Harvey!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Let's play "Feud."
Give me Ernie. Give me Jimmy.
♪♪
All right, fellas.
Here we go.
We got top seven answers on
the board.
"If you live to be 100,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
Sleeping.
-We're gonna play!
-Yeah.
Gonna play.
He's gonna play.
Let's go.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Ernie Johnson has hosted "Inside
the NBA" since 1990, everybody.
And one of the great
inspirational stories
I've heard in a long time.
Ah, you're very kind.
I appreciate you.
-Kenny "The Jet"!
-Yes, sir!
-This is my man.
-Yes, sir.
Former NBA point guard,
two-time world champ
with the Houston Rockets.
Yeah, two-time world champ.
And benefit of
two guys next to me,
'cause our teams
actually beat them.
Oh, my bad. I'm sorry.
We're on the wrong show.
I -- That's not this show.
That's not this show.
My bad, my bad.
[ Laughter ]
It's not this show. I told you.
Yeah, yeah, it won't --
This gonna be a problem
over here, man.
My bad. All right.
Let's go.
"You live to be 100.
What do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
-Watching a movie.
Good answer!
Thank you.
"Good answer.
Good answer."
Well, we don't know
that yet.
There it is.
-Thank you. Over here.
-See -- See --
Steve: "Celebrity Family
Feud" is different.
When he gives the answer,
Kenny told him,
"You're supposed to say
'Good answer, good answer.'"
Charles say,
"We don't know that yet."
[ Laughter ]
-Shaq, how you feel, man?
-I'm feeling good.
Glad to be here.
'Bout to bust these guys up.
[ Laughter ]
Welcome to the show.
15 times All-Star,
Hall of Famer,
7-time leading point
scorer in the NBA.
Kenny: Wow.
-"The Diesel."
-Yes.
Omega Psi Phi!
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right, Shaq.
"You live to be 100.
What do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
Chillin' with
the grandchildren.
-Good answer.
Ernie: Oh.
Not so good answer.
You ain't got
no grandkids at 100?
Good answer!
good answer!
Don't none of you
got no grandkids?
-Come on.
-Come on, Chuckster.
Was that good?
Good answer!
Shaq's like, "You 100 years old,
and you ain't got no grandkids?"
Yeah, Shaq, you 100, you gonna
have grandkids, but they 40.
Anyway, let me get you...
Charles Barkley.
Power forward for Philadelphia,
Phoenix, and Houston.
NBA Hall of Famer.
And 1993 NBA MVP.
-Yeah!
-Charles Barkley.
How you feelin', man?
I ain't gonna lie, man.
I'm a little nervous.
-You a little nervous?
-I'm a little nervous.
You know, we've seen
this show a long time, man,
but being here in person,
I'm a little nervous.
I ain't gonna lie.
-You should be.
-The good thing about it --
I actually like
the way things are.
I get a chance to catch
my breath and think here.
-Mm.
-Ah. That'd be a first.
Oh, my bad.
Wrong show again, Steve.
This the wrong side
over here.
[ Laughter ]
Come on, Chuck.
"You live to be 100, man,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
Having a nice meal.
Chuck is on the board!
-Hey!
-There you go, Chuck.
Chuck is
on the board, baby!
All right, Kristen.
"You live to be 100,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
Having a nice drink.
-Having a drink.
-Good answer!
Some Ensure.
Ernie, only one strike.
"You live to be 100,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
Uh, reading.
Let's see if it's up there.
Reading.
D'oh! My bad. Man!
All right. We got to
slow down, fellas.
Look, we got two
strikes against.
MLB can steal.
Jet, if you live
to be 100,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?
Looking for a date.
Ohh.
Hey.
MLB, get ready.
[ Laughter ]
Get ready, MLB.
See? This is not
how you play the game.
You're supposed to
support your team.
He said, "Looking for a date."
They went, "Ah..."
[ Laughter ]
Kenny old ass gonna be
looking for a date!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Thank you!
Thank you! Thank you.
[ Laughter ]
Shaq, two strikes.
Major League Baseball can steal.
"If you live to be 100,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
He already said sex.
I was gonna say
poppin' VIAGRA pills,
but you can't say that one.
-So I'm gonna go with...
-Like Chiclets.
Yeah, just --
Just. Yeah.
[ Laughter ]
-I'm gonna go with walking --
-Like they're pumpkin seeds.
You just...
I'm going with walking.
-Walking?
-Exercising.
Walking and exercising.
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right, y'all. Here we go.
"If you live to be 100,
what do you think you'll be
doing on Saturday night?"
Steve, we're gonna go
with playing board games
with the homies.
Playing board games
with the homies!
Good answer, Jimmy.
Good answer.
♪♪
-Yes!
-Number 4.
All: Dancing!
Let's go to question 2.
Give me Kenny. Give me Johnny.
♪♪
All right, fellas. We got top
eight answers on the board.
Here we go.
"If a man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
-His shirt.
-A jacket.
All right.
We're gonna play, right?
Yeah, we're gonna play!
Yeah, we're gonna play.
All right.
We're gonna play, Steve.
All right, Shaq. "If a man's
zipper breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
-The Good Book.
-Oh!
Hey! Good answer.
-Good answer, brother.
-The Good Book!
Kenny: Good answer.
There you go. There you go.
You done broke
the ice, Chuck.
You've been on the
board already, baby.
"If a man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
A child.
-Oh.
-Whoa!
-A what?
-A child!
Shaq: The man gonna
get us locked up.
Not a good answer.
Put your hands
behind your back.
-You're under arrest.
-Not a good answer.
Not a good answer!
Not a good answer.
Come over here.
[ Laughter ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
I meant a baby!
Shh! Even worse!
Even worse.
Then he tried to fix it!
He said, "I meant a baby."
Kenny: That's worse!
That's worse!
[ Laughs ]
Oh, God.
This is on YouTube.
You know what's crazy?
It's probably gonna
be up there, though.
Somebody's child!
Yeah!
-I told you.
-Yes.
"Person" sounds better.
Child? Baby?
Damn, Chuck.
All right, Kristen. Sorry.
You have to follow this.
[ Laughs ] Yeah.
"If a man's zipper
breaks at church,
other than somebody's baby, what
might he use to cover it up?"
The collection
offering plate?
offering plate.
Kenny: Good answer.
That's what I would do.
[ Laughs ] Ernie.
"Man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
How 'bout the, uh --
the bulletin that...
You get the bulletin
when you go in.
The bulletin.
Church announcements.
All right.
Only one strike, Kenny.
"A man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
I don't have one in today,
but normally I would --
A hankie.
His handkerchief.
A handkerchief.
Oh!
Now, I don't normally
root for teams,
but, Shaq, if you could
please get this one
so I could just hear
what he gonna say next.
[ Laughter ]
If you could just somehow,
Shaq, pull this one out.
'Cause I can't wait to hear
what "Mr. Baby"
comes up with again.
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right, Shaq.
"If a man's zipper breaks --"
Hey, y'all can get ready
to steal. Two strikes.
"A man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
-I'm-a gonna go with the hand.
-The hand.
Good answer, Shaq.
Good answer. Good answer.
The hand!
[ Cheers and applause ]
Ernie: Uh-oh.
Prayer changes things.
And here we are again.
Oh, ain't this
where I need to be.
Come on,
Charles Barkley.
"If a man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
Now, we already got
the baby there.
The fan.
The little wand fan.
-The fan.
-Yeah.
That's a good --
I like it.
-The fan!
-Thataway, Chuckster.
That was a good answer.
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right, Major League
Baseball. Here's your chance.
"If a man's zipper
breaks at church,
what might he use
to cover it up?"
-His wife's purse.
-His wife's purse!
Good answer, Jimmy.
Good answer.
♪♪
Number 8.
All: Safety pin!
That -- No.
Number 5.
All: Hat!
Well, we'll be right back with
more "Celebrity Family Feud."
All right. Welcome back to
the "Celebrity Family Feud."
We got a good one.
"Inside the NBA" got 90.
Major League Baseball
All-Stars got 77.
Give me Shaq. Give me Sean.
♪♪
That's a big hand
right there, Shaq.
-You know it is.
-Man.
Steve: Yeah, yeah.
Point values are double, fellas.
Top six answers on the board.
Here we go.
We asked 100 married women
to fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big..." what?
-Kiss.
Shaq?
I can't say the answer
I want to say, so...
[ Laughter ]
So I'm gonna say gift.
I'm gonna just say gift.
[ Laughter ]
I'm gonna say gift.
Gonna say gift.
"Gift." Big ol' gift!
-We'll play. We're gonna play.
-All right. They're gonna play.
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Hey, Jennie.
-Hey.
Jennie Finch, one of the
most famous softball players
in the history
of the game, folks.
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right. Let's go.
This is right up your alley.
100 married women.
Fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big" what?
-Hug.
-A big hug.
Johnny Franco. 22 years.
Left-handed relief
pitcher, everybody.
424 career saves.
That's the closer, baby.
That's the dude, when they go
out, they walk out to the mound.
They do a quick trot
from way out there.
That's all I want to do.
Somebody do that,
and I trot
all the way out.
All right, Johnny. We talked
to 100 married women.
Fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big" what?
A big meal.
-Cooked meal.
-A big meal.
Hmm.
What say, Jimmy?
This is Jimmy Rollins,
everybody.
Three-time All-Star
and the 2007
National League MVP.
Whoo!
Shorty got down.
Jimmy, talked to
100 married women.
Fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big" what?
Mm. I'm-a go with...
massage.
Big massage!
Jimmy: Hey!
Johnny Damon, baby.
That's a bad boy right here.
World Series rings with
the Red Sox and the Ya--
Oh, you got 'em on.
Ahh.
Ooh!
Oh, you got the Boston
and the Yan--
That's hard to do.
Them two together.
I don't know how
you did that.
I donated one of 'em.
You helped him out
a little bit?
Philadelphia donated
one to us.
All right, Johnny.
Come on, man.
We talked to 100 married women.
Fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big" what?
-Surprise?
-A big surprise.
Sean. The nicest guy
in baseball.
Hey, Sean. [ Laughs ]
Major-league first baseman.
12 seasons in the league,
everybody.
He's known as "The Mayor"
'cause he's one of the
nicest guys in baseball.
Sean, we got to be careful.
We got two strikes.
NBA, get ready to steal.
Talked to 100 married women.
Fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big" what?
-Party.
-A big party!
Big party.
-Come on!
-What's going on here?
[ Cheers and applause ]
Steve:
Let's go. Let's go.
-All right. Here we go.
-Vacation. Vacation.
We got a chance to steal.
We talked to 100 married women.
Fill in the blank.
"I like it when my man
gives me a big" what?
-I'm gonna say vacation.
-I think smile.
-I think -- I like smile.
-I like that, too.
-A big smile.
They went with
the lady and Chuck.
Smile!
Number 4.
All: Compliment!
Well, let's move on
to the next question.
Give me Charles Barkley!
Give me Jennie.
♪♪
Johnny: Come on, Jennie.
Box him out.
Point values are triple.
Here we go.
We got top four answers
on the board.
We talked to 100 single men.
Fill in the blank.
"My ideal wife would have to
be both hot and" what?
-Smart.
-Sexy.
-I like that. I like that.
-Good try. Good try. Good try.
-Good try.
-All right, John.
Talked to 100 single men.
Fill in the blank.
"My ideal wife would have
to be both hot and" what?
In shape.
-Strong. Strong.
-She's hot and in shape.
Mm. Jimmy, we only
got one strike.
Talked to 100 single men.
Fill in the blank.
"My ideal wife would have
to be both hot and" blank.
-A great cook.
-Hot and a great cook.
All right.
We got two strikes now.
Got to slow it down
a little bit, Johnny.
We got to be careful. If it's
not there, NBA can steal.
100 single men.
Fill in the blank.
"My ideal wife would have
to be both hot and" what?
-She's got be nice, Steve.
-Hot and nice.
Yeah. I like that.
Sean. It's down with you.
We got two strikes.
If it's there,
you're still alive.
If it's not there,
the NBA can steal.
Talked to 100 single men.
Fill in the blank.
"My ideal wife would have
to be both hot and" what?
And confident, Steve.
She's got to be confident!
Hot and confident!
Sean: Dang!
Ernie:
Let's go. Let's go.
Well...
NBA, here's the deal.
If it's there, your team steals,
your team wins the game.
If it's not there,
the other team
gets a chance to play
Sudden Death.
-Ernie?
-What did we decide?
-I like funny.
-We asked 100 single men.
-Or rich.
-Funny or rich.
-Fill in the blank.
-I would go with funny.
-"My ideal wife..."
-Hot, sexy, and funny.
I like the way they
discuss it out loud.
-Let's do funny.
-Fill in the blank.
"My ideal wife would have
to be both hot and" what?
-Funny.
We're gonna go
with hot and funny!
♪♪
Number 4.
All: Loyal!
Number 3.
All: Rich!
-Charles had it, man.
-Dummy over here said funny.
Charles had it. He was scared,
and he got all the answers.
He got scared,
and he said them all.
Why you listening
to Kenny and Shaq, man?
-Aw, no, no.
-Go with your heart.
Chuck, you know all this.
Well, no.
His heart was "sexy."
His initial answer was "sexy."
Let's not forget that.
[ Laughter ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
All right.
Nobody reached 300 points,
so we gonna play Sudden Death.
Give me Kristen. Give me John.
♪♪
For this survey, we're asking
for the top answer only.
Name something specific
that might come in a 6-pack.
-Beer.
Kristen!
♪♪
Hey! I need two of y'all
to play Fast Money.
Hey, thanks for playing, fellas.
We're gonna make a donation
to your charity
just for being
good sports, guys.
We'll be right back with...
[ Laughing hysterically ]
This about to be the worst game
of Fast Money you've ever seen!
Please watch this!
We'll be right back.
[ Laughing ] Oh!
Oh, this is too good.
Come on, Chuck. You can
do it, baby. You ready?
I'm ready.
We got 20 seconds
on the clock, please.
Here we go.
We asked 100 married women,
"If it were up to you,
how many nights a week
would you make love?"
Three.
"Name something specific
on a football player
that might be too tight."
Uh, jersey.
"Name something you need before
you start cooking barbecue."
Charcoal.
Fill in the blank.
"Fortune" blank.
500.
"Name a drink that's served
both hot and cold."
Tea.
[ Cheers and applause ]
Come on, Chuck!
Come on, boy.
You about to get
a little something here.
Good answers!
Yeah.
You might be all right.
We asked 100 married women,
"If it were up to you,
how many nights a week
would you make love?"
You said...
Survey said...
Yeah.
"Name something specific
on a football player
that might be too tight."
You said...
Survey said...
"Name something you need before
you start cooking barbecue."
You said...
Survey said...
Fill in the blank.
"Fortune" blank.
You said...
Survey said...
Yeah.
"Name a drink that's
served both hot and cold."
You said...
Survey said...
Oh, yeah.
Go get it, boy.
♪♪
Here comes Shaq!
How'd Chuck do?
He do all right?
Chuck did a'ight, man.
Chuck got 134 points.
-Man.
-Yeah.
You need 66, Diesel.
You ready?
-Yes, sir.
-All right.
Let's remind everybody
of Chuck's answers.
25 seconds on the clock,
please.
All right.
Here we go.
We asked 100 married women,
"If it were up to you,
how many nights a week
would you make love?"
Four.
"Name something specific
on a football player
that might be too tight."
Pads.
"Name something you need before
you start cooking barbecue."
Barbecue sauce.
Fill in the blank.
"Fortune" blank.
500.
-Try again.
-Fortune cookie.
"Name a drink that's served
both hot and cold."
-Tea.
-Try again.
Coffee.
Yeah!
[ Cheers and applause ]
-We won?
-About to see.
Normally, I put my arm
around the person,
but this ain't
gonna look good.
[ Laughter ]
[ Cheers and applause ]
That was a very
uncomfortable moment.
All right.
We need 66 points. Let's go.
We asked 100 married women,
"If it were up to you,
how many nights a week
would you make love?"
You said...
Survey said...
One -- One was
the number-one answer.
-One?
-Aw, hell no.
You know they're
tired of you.
Stop all this four times,
three times, man.
Come on.
"Name something specific
on a football player
that might be too tight."
You said...
[ As Shaq ] Pants.
[ Laughter ]
[ Normal voice ]
Survey said...
[ Cheers and applause ]
-Shaq!
-You got this!
Diesel!
We 9 points away.
Number-one answer
was pants. All right.
"Name something you need before
you start cooking barbecue."
You said...
You need barbecue sauce.
Man, he can't even start
without knowing where
the damn sauce is.
Damn the grill,
charcoal.
Unh-unh. Where the hell
is the sauce?
[ Laughter ]
Survey said...
[ Cheers and applause ]
♪♪
Grill and smoker was
the number-one answer.
Fortune cookie was
Tea was the number-one answer.
They had all of them.
Well, that's 25,000 bucks
for the Mustard Seed School.
I'd like to thank
Ernie and Jimmy
and the rest of everybody,
all of you guys, for coming out
and joining us on
"Celebrity Family Feud."
Stay tuned for two new families
when "Celebrity Family Feud"
continues!
I'm Steve Harvey.
We'll see you shortly.